post css a tool for transforming styles with javascript plugins when you build a
發布 css 一個用於在構建網站時使用 javascript 插件轉換樣式的工具
website the css code you write is rarely the code that you actually want to ship
您編寫的 css代碼很少是您實際想要發送
to the browser the developer wants to write code with modern features that
到瀏覽器的代碼 開發人員希望編寫具有現代功能的代碼，以
maximize productivity but end users want fast minified code that supports legacy
最大限度地提高生產力，但最終用戶希望快速 支持舊版
browsers post css is a build tool that makes everybody happy it can take a css
瀏覽器的壓縮代碼 post css 是一個讓每個人都高興的構建工具，它可以獲取一個 css
file and convert it to an abstract syntax tree then provides an api where
文件並將其轉換為抽象語法樹，然後提供一個 api，其中
plugins written in javascript can produce a different output for example
用 javascript 編寫的插件可以產生不同的輸出，例如
by using the auto prefixer plugin you'll never have to worry about writing vendor
通過使用 auto  prefixer 插件，您再也不必擔心
prefixes on your styles ever again or with the preset enb plugin you can write
在樣式上編寫供應商前綴，或者使用預設的 enb 插件，您可以編寫
modern css while post css will automatically add the polyfills needed
現代 css，而 post css 將自動添加
to support your targeted browsers or you might drop in a tool like style and to
支持目標瀏覽器所需的 polyfill，或者您可能會放入一個工具 喜歡風格並在
detect issues before they break your ui and there are tons of other useful
問題破壞您的用戶界面之前檢測問題
plugins in the ecosystem to try out and if none of them meet your needs you can
，並且生態系統中有大量其他有用的插件可供嘗試，如果沒有 它們中的任何一個都不能滿足您的需求您可以
always build your own you might use the plugin api to find all the color
隨時構建自己的您可以使用插件 api 來查找
declarations in the code then write some javascript to transform them to a
代碼中的所有顏色聲明，然後編寫一些javascript 將它們轉換為
different format you probably already use post css without even realizing it
您可能已經使用 post css 的不同格式，甚至沒有意識到
as it generates more npm downloads than typescript and webpack can bind it's
它 生成的 npm 下載量比typescript 和 webpack 可以綁定更多，它
used under the hood by frameworks like veed and next js to provide a
被veed 和 next js 等框架在後台使用，以提供
streamlined developer experience and it's also used by some of the world's
簡化的開發人員體驗，而且它現在也被一些世界上
most popular websites like wikipedia and twitter now despite its name it also
最受歡迎的網站（如 wikipedia 和twitter）使用，儘管它的名字也
handles pre-processing similar to frameworks like sas less and stylus it
處理類似於 sas less 和 stylus 等框架的預處理它
can be used in conjunction with existing preprocessors or as an alternative to
可以與現有的預處理器結合使用，或者
them altogether if you want to write css with nesting or mixins there are plugins
如果你想用嵌套或 mixins 編寫 css，則可以完全替代它們，有一些
that can enable those features in your code so it's like configuring your own
插件可以在你的代碼中啟用這些功能，所以 這就像
css preprocessor by including your favorite features and avoiding the ones
通過包含您最喜歡的功能並
that tend to lead to bad practices on top of that it tends to produce much
避免可能導致不良實踐的功能來配置您自己的 CSS 預處理器最重要的是，它往往會產生
faster build times to get started install it into your project with npm
更快的構建時間，以便開始使用 npm 將其安裝到您的項目中，
then create a post css config file inside of it customize the array of
然後在其中創建一個 post css 配置文件自
plugins that you want to use and finally run it from the command line as part of
定義您要使用的插件數組，最後從命令運行它 作為
your build process to make your styles production ready this has been post css
您的構建過程的一部分，以使您的樣式生產準備就緒，這已
in 100 seconds if you want to see more short videos like this hit the like
在 100 秒內發布 css 如果您想看到更多這樣的短視頻，請點擊喜歡
button and subscribe thanks for watching and i will see you in the next one
按鈕並訂閱感謝觀看，我會在下一個